wildwalks.com 2018-12-14

# Privacy | Wildwalks

## Privacy

##### Your Privacy

Wildwalks aims to comply with the Privacy and Personal Information Protection Act 1998 (NSW), which regulates the collection, storage, quality, use and disclosure of personal information.

**Wildwalks App subscriptions**

To help us continue making this app awesome and to allow us to continue to add more wonderful walks we charge users to access longer walks in this app. 

There are two subscriptions length options Monthly or Annual. Once subscribed you get unlimited access to all the information on the walks displayed in the app. You can then download the maps, photos and tracknotes so that the app will work offline.    
The current price of each subscription is available on the updates page and is displayed in Australian dollars. Payment will be charged to iTunes Account at confirmation of purchase.  Subscription automatically renews unless auto-renew is turned off at least 24-hours before the end of the current period.  Your Itunes account will be charged for renewal within 24-hours prior to the end of the current period at the same price. Your subscriptions may be managed and auto-renewal may be turned off by going to your Itunes Account Settings after purchase.

##### Use and disclosure of personal information.

Information that in some way identifies you may be gathered when you use our website or send us an email.

##### Collection of information

**Information collected from browsing** When you view the Wildwalks website and app, we may collect the following information: • your IP (Internet protocol) address or host name eg. 123.123.123.12 or xxx.yyy.com.au • the date and time you visited the website • the pages or documents you download • the web browser, operating system, screen resolution, Internet settings you are using • the previous site you visited, if you reached our website by clicking on a link • whether you have previously visited our website (only if you accept Cookies).   **Information collected from online forms** When you submit a form on the Wildwalks website we collect information from it. This information may include personal and organisational details such as your full name, phone number, business name and ACN details, email address and street address. Clicking on the ‘submit’ button on any form acts as your consent for Wildwalks to collect the information you have provided. Before you submit this information we will take reasonable steps to inform you of: • where applicable, any law that requires the particular information to be collected • which fields are mandatory and which are optional. **Information collected from email** If you send us an email, we will record your email and email address for the purpose of responding to you.

##### Use and disclosure of information collected

Information collected from web browsing is used to identify patterns of usage of the Wildwalks website and app. This will help us improve the website and the services offered we offer. Information collected from forms and email will only be used for the purpose for which you have provided it. We will not use it for any other purpose, nor will we disclose it, unless with your consent or in other circumstances where such use or disclosure is permitted under the Privacy and Personal Information Protection Act 1998. Your personal information (including your email address) will not be automatically added to a mailing list, or sold or otherwise transferred to a third party. We take reasonable steps to protect information during transfer and storage. Physical measures, such as building and equipment security, are used in conjunction with digital technology, such as data encryption and firewalls, to minimise unauthorised access to information.

  * Wildwalks uses Google Analytics including Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting to help monitor, report, understand and improve the service.
  * Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).
  * we also use Facebook Pixel
